A Guide to the Promotional Plans for Fairfax County Housing Developments Collection, 1986-2015
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Promotional Plans for Fairfax County Housing Developments Collection, 1986-2015
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 02-07
0.5 linear feet
The Promotional Plans for Fairfax County Housing Developments Collection consists of 0.5 linear feet and spans the years 1986-2015 and consists of promotional brochures and booklets featuring renderings and images of planned housing developments.
Virginia Room staff
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Collection assembled over a period of years by Virginia Room staff
Historical and Biographical Information
Fairfax County Public Library’s Virginia Room has been collecting promotional plans for Fairfax County housing developments for a period of years. The collection is continuously being added to.
Scope and Content
The Promotional Plans for Fairfax County Housing Developments Collection consists of 0.5 linear feet and spans the years 1986-2015 and consists of promotional brochures and booklets featuring renderings and images of planned housing developments. The majority of promotional plans in this collection are for Sully Station, a planned community in Centreville, Virginia. A promotional booklet for IDI Group Companies contains photographs of a variety of housing and retail projects completed during the 1980s-1990s.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Housing - Virginia - Fairfax County; Real estate development - Virginia - Fairfax County
Container List
- Sully Station, Kettler & Scott Planned Community, Centreville, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sully Station, Signature Communities Inc., Centreville, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sully Station, Long Homes of Virginia, Inc., Centreville, Va., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NV Homes at Sully Station, Centreville, Va., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Van Metre at Sully Station, Centreville, Va., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Sully Station, Fairfield Homes, Inc., Centreville, Va., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Glenberry Townhomes, William L. Berry & Company, Inc., Centreville, Va., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- IDI Group Companies - The Fairways at Leisure World, The Belvedere, Montebello, Altavista, The Rotonda, Burke Cove, Porto Vecchio, Parkfairfax, Belle View, Parc East, The Plaza, Techworld Plaza, Rosslyn Center, Ballston Metro Center, 8200 Greensboro Drive, 650 Massachusetts Avenue, Burke Centre, Franklin Farm, Vista International Hotel, Ramada Renaissance Ballston, Ramada Renaissance Techworld, The Atrium at Ballston Metro, Rosslyn Center Arcade, The Shops at Techworld Plaza, Build America, Leisureworld Plaza, c. 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Farrcroft Old Town Fairfax, Basheer & Edgemoore, Fairfax, Va., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Park Glen, Van Metre Homes, Burke, Va., 2015 (Box 1, Folder 10)